http://www.bettercomputers.com.au/privacy.php

Home / Privacy Notice
Categories
AccessoriesAmplifiersCables & AdaptorsCasesDigital CamcordersDigital CamerasDIY HTPC PartsHome Theatre PC'sHome AutomationProjectorsSpeakersTVs
Manufacturers
Please SelectAbitACTAntecASUSAvermediaAywunBluegearsBurr BrownCadenceCorsairDa-LiteDatamasterDelta Electronics IncDuratechDvicoEmbedded AutomationEon3EpsonGenericGeniusGilkonHauppaugeHighPointHush TechnologiesIntelLeadtekLindyLogitechMaestroMarmitekMatchmasterMicrosoftMitsubishiMonster CableNational SemiconductorNostalgia ElectricsOrigenAEPanasonicPretecRepotecSamsungSapphire TechnologyServisolShuttleSilverstoneSimplifi digitalSonySunixThermalrightThermaltakeTP-LinkVerbatimW HomeWestern DigitalWhatmoughZalman
Quick Find
Use keywords to find the product you're looking for
What's New?
Samsung UA32D5000 32inch Full HD 5000 Series LED TV$800.00
Polls
Do you own a 3D TV?Yes, I love it!Yes, but I mainly use it as a 2D TVNo, but I will be buying one in the next 12 monthsNo, I'm not really interested in 3D TV
[ Results ]
RSS Feeds
Latest News
What's New?
Categories
What is RSS?
SSL Security Info
You are viewing a part of our web site that does not require a secure connection.
What is SSL?
Privacy Notice
Better Computers knows that you
care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust
and want you to feel confident in our services and security as it relates to your
personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Better Computers,
you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.
Personal Information
The information we learn
from customers helps us personalise and continually improve your shopping experience
at Better Computers. Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give
Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or
give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information,
but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.
We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to
your requests, fulfilling orders, customising future shopping for you, improving
our store features, and communication with you.
Automatic Information:
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with
our website. For example, like many web sites, we sometimes use "cookies,"
and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses
our website.
E-mail Communications:
To help us make e-mails more productive to improve service and your shopping
experience, we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products,
notifications of changes to our policies, and order confirmations. If you
do not want to receive e-mail from us, other than order notifications and
receipts, please adjust your "Subscription" preferences by logging
into your account.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric
identifier text files that we transfer to your computers hard drive through
your Web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser and to provide
features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
Sharing Information
We respect your privacy
and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever provide your account contact
or payment information to any third party vendor, associate or service provider
unless absolutely necessary in order to complete your transaction and order.
Information Security
We work to protect the security
of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL)
software, which encrypts information you provide to us for purchasing of our
products or services. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card
numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card
number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. It is
important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and
to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer
by clicking the "log off" link located in the side menu.
Access to Information
Better Computers gives you access
to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with
us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
Terms & Conditions, Notices and Revisions
If you choose to visit Better Computers, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and
our Terms & Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes,
and application of the law of the state of our local state. If you have any
concern about privacy of your personal information as used and collected within
our website, please send us a thorough description by clicking on the "Contact
Us" link on the side menu, and we will try to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly,
and our Privacy Notice and the Terms & Conditions will change also. We may e-mail
periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed
us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information
that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make,
however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make
them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the
consent of affected customers.
Information You Give Us
You provide most such information
when you search, buy, order, post reviews, or other methods of communication
via our website or email to Better Computers. As a result of those actions, you might
supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers, and
credit card information.
Credit Card Fraud
We take credit card fraud very seriously at Better Computers and will report any
cases of Credit Card fraud to the Authorities, along with all the information we have
about the fraudster.
Automatic Information
For security purposes Better Computers sometimes collects and analyses the Internet protocol (IP) address used
to connect your computer to the Internet, and to our website. This is done for
your protection for tracking purposes in the unfortunate event that someone
gains access to your personal or financial information and opens an account,
or makes purchases under your name.
Questions
Questions regarding our Privacy Notice, Privacy Policy, or other policy related material can be
directed to our support staff by emailing Better Computers from the Contact Us
page.
Latest News
New Usana Canada Store!
Merry Christmas!
Holiday Trading Hours
New Usana New Zealand Store
Sponsored Links
Specials
Datamaster Premium F-Type to F-Type Antenna Cable, M/M, 10m$26.95$26.40
Currencies
Australian DollarUS DollarBritish Pound
Renting
How to Rent?
Friday 11 December, 2020
Product List | Site Map
Terms & Conditions | Privacy Notice | Reward Points | Payment & Credit Cards | Shipping & Returns | News | Contact UsAffiliate Terms & Conditions | Affiliate Program | Affiliate Login
and
follow us @hometheatrepc
become a fan
Copyright © 2004-2020 Better Computers Australia Pty LtdAll prices, specifications, availability, and terms of offers are subject to change without notice.Stock Status is updated once daily and products marked as In Stock could be sold out at time of purchase.Images are for illustration purposes only and may not represent actual products.Buy USANA Essentials or USANA Healthpak from our health store.
